<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[fineartimage]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[fineartimage]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/fineartimage/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 15:41:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/fineartimage/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everything is Art-Everything is Politics -]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Everything is Art-Everything is Politics -</h1><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fcf5db02-bc87-4ad4-8aa1-c14a0109df12.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fcf5db02-bc87-4ad4-8aa1-c14a0109df12.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9841d284-38f4-4ea0-97cb-00d8ae8dd2f7</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 15:41:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[At Fine Art Image we seek to express the beauty of the Natural World. Our visual artists create evocative images of the Natural World that have a sense of mystery, and resonate with the energy of light. Our mission is to capture the fragile beauty of our]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>At Fine Art Image we seek to express the beauty of the Natural World. Our visual artists create evocative images of the Natural World that have a sense of mystery, and resonate with the energy of light. Our mission is to capture the fragile beauty of our environment while encouraging efforts for its preservation. Currently, we are developing new visual projects while traveling the world. In Eastern Kentucky we created images of farm communities in transition. In Afghanistan we explored the plight of children in orphanages and refugee camps in countries torn by war or natural disaster. In the concrete jungles of American cities we examine the growing issue of hunger and the homeless. In Central America we captured the vibrancy of street vendors and Farmers Markets. Our images are informed and inspired by our recognition of the interconnectedness of all things. ©2016 fine art image | all rights reserved | fineartimage11@gmail.com | 631.238.4327</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/fineartimage/at-fine-art-image-we-seek-to-express-the-beauty-of-the-natur/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">37f564fb-1d71-4ef5-bbc3-8b71e335c788</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 15:34:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>